{
    "subject": "resource/Albanian_Republic",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Albanian_lek",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Albania Republic is Albanian lek.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9781244993209839,
            "question": "Is the lek the official currency of Albania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9455292820930481,
            "question": "Which country uses the Albanian lek as its currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.933706521987915,
            "question": "Name the official currency of Albania."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8704261779785156,
            "question": "What is the currency of Albania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8550218939781189,
            "question": "Does Albania use a different currency besides the lek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7757714986801147,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the currency used in Albania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7743262052536011,
            "question": "What name is given to the Albanian currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7034797072410583,
            "question": "How is the Albanian lek represented?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.66545170545578,
            "question": "What is another name for the Albanian lek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5818629860877991,
            "question": "What is the symbol for the Albanian lek?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Albania Republic is Albanian lek.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9276_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is another name for the Albanian lek?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9276_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is the Albanian lek represented?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9276_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What name is given to the Albanian currency?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9276_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9276_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: All the documents provided contain information about the Albanian Lek being the official currency of Albania, with the symbol L, and its introduction in 1926. Therefore, the statement \"The currency of Albania Republic is Albanian lek\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain information about the official currency of Albania being the Albanian Lek (ALL), which supports the statement that \"The currency of Albania Republic is Albanian lek.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}